earlier this season I talked about a
shuttle train at London's Heathrow
Airport with its own Twitter handle this
is the terminal 5 transport train asking
me to follow it on
Twitter to be clear this isn't the train
to the airport this is the train that
takes you 400 yard from the terminal to
baggage claim it's basically an elevator
on its
side after we mentioned on our show the
T5 Transit Twitter feed blew up in fact
it's gotten so big that it's got its own
action movie
franchise yeah I mean I I didn't even
want to come to England but I just had
to ride that horizontal
elevator I
just drawn to
it in a world where a train leavs the
station and then comes back like every
60 seconds I was born BN on that train
and I'll die on that train T5 Transit
falls into the wrong hands I am telling
you it's like disaster blood fam R
everything awful it's the equivalent to
everyone having STDs stand clear the
closing doors
but mostly people will be
just delayed in getting their
B you have to take it you have no choice
damn
it the music on this train
sucks get off my
train on the
T5 sometimes love is arriving why can't
a woman love a
train and sometimes it's
departing next up murder this summer or
next summer or anytime you fly into
Heathrow Airport things are about to go
on the
RS you ask for a
miracle I give you this train t five
team Furious watch out for the
[Applause]
[Music]
train